<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eli Le</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eli Le</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python? In MY RStudio? (It&#39;s More Likely Than You Think)</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/python-in-my-rstudio-it-s-more-likely-than-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/python-in-my-rstudio-it-s-more-likely-than-you-think/</guid>
      <description>(Picture of Samuel L. Jackson in a meme that says “Snakes? On my plane? It’s more likely than you think.” This meme format parodies an old ad for “Net Nanny” website blocking software.)
  Have you ever thought to yourself, “sure, R is great, but what I really need is a way to make my life more complicated by adding Python into the mix”? Sure you have! Luckily for you, there’s an R package that lets you run Python right in RStudio and even have the two programming languages “talk” to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Eli Le 0. Introduction The fifth main game in Nintendo’s Animal Crossing series, Animal Crossing: New Horizons is a life simulation video game published on March 20, 2020 for the Nintendo Switch. Partially because it was released in the first few weeks of the COVID-19 pandemic and partially because it’s just super cute, the game became wildly popular in 2020 as people looked for a way to connect with friends and escape everything going on in the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Eli Le 0. Introduction I’ve been a big fan of Taylor Swift’s music since I was in elementary school. Over the years she’s released nine albums across a variety of genres, ranging from country to synth-pop to alternative rock. To get some more insight into the lyrics and audio features associated with Taylor Swift’s discography, I made a Spotify playlist using songs from Taylor Swift’s nine studio albums and used spotifyr to extract data associated with each song.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis (Taylor Swift)
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction (Animal Crossing)
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
